I am 3/4 of the way through and I'm
drawing a bit of a blank so I kind of
had four or five my genes in a row that
was like no no she's Mary cuz I've
shared a lot of them and I've also said
that way he came through share it but it
was more you've already done that or
that doesn't quite make sense so I'm
looking and I have a advent calendar in
my room with chocolate it's I'm saving
it for December
it's got it on sale and it's good
chocolate I feel like there's something
around advent calendars I do not make
calendar for my child
and I don't want to have chocolate every
day so I write our own up and so I
usually go to the dollar store and buy
different things that I can then put in
and so one would be coordinating that
with other people so that maybe one
parent because I mean I love having
things more making more yeah so one
parent could make stuff for day one for
everyone day two for everyone and it's
all homemade and adorable and better
than stuff in winning at the dollar
store so coordinating and thing is if
any of these ideas what I want to create
as a system or would anyone has an idea
like that you can put it out there and
like instantly nearly instantly you get
twenty other parents who are like or 24
I guess that would make sense right now
24 parents you want to do that since
there's 24 days in an advent calendar
but you can make it out of a calendar
for absolutely anything any holiday get
other people that celebrate that holiday
with you and ideas for what could be in
each one and if it oh but if I had that
idea which have no had and I want to put
it out there that it's super easy to
offer an idea and have people either say
like that's the stupidest idea ever
who wants to make an admin calendar full
of cute adorable crafts for your kid to
do already haven't been made or which
I'm guessing it's more the case there
might even be 90% of people who do that
by the 10% like
I'd love to do that and jump on board
with it but it's a more easier Avenue
because I could do that I can put that
on Facebook by itself but having a route
to be able to easily put your ideas out
into the world have them tested along
the way and created together is amazing
and I think it brings us much further in
society and not just cause it creates
advent calendars because clearly that's
a perk and not a necessity so 75 the
Apple is a little bit a plug for the
system itself and a let's work together
to create fun advent calendars